ourlounge.co.uk 2017-07-17

# McDonalds Privacy Policy

**McDonald's Restaurants Ltd ourlounge Privacy Policy**

McDonald's Restaurants Limited, referred to in this policy as "we", "us" or "our", are pleased to provide information to all of our employees and alumni about our online privacy policy. Please be assured that we use our best efforts to protect the privacy of visitors to this web site.

**Types of Information We Collect and How It Is Used**

We only collect and use personal information, such as first and last names, addresses and email addresses from you. In addition, we may also gather date of birth and mobile phone details where you voluntarily provide this information to us.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

We may share personal information within the McDonald's Family; by this expression, we mean McDonald's Corporation and each of its subsidiaries, together with their respective franchisees and certain selected companies.

Those selected companies are either our partners who perform a function such as prize-provision within our promotions and offers, or are agencies and suppliers whom we have retained to assist us to more effectively fulfill orders, manage and conduct promotions and offers, provide technical assistance and support and perform other functions to support our marketing activities.

All selected companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform such functions, but will only be permitted by us to use such personal information for the purpose of performing that function (which may include one to which you have expressly given your consent) and not for any other purpose.

We will only transfer personal information about you outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) to the extent that it is permitted under all privacy and communications legislation applicable within the UK.   By submitting your personal information to us, you agree to the transfer, storing or processing of your information outside of the EEA.

In all cases, any use of your personal information by the McDonald's Family which use has been instigated by us (as opposed, for example, to a promotional partner), will comply with this policy.

Occasionally, with your permission and depending on the purpose for and context in which you gave that permission, we will send marketing information and news to you, for example, relating to new product offerings, loyalty schemes and clubs, discount coupons and other promotions and offers. This may include our sending to you marketing information for the products or services of a promotional partner on that partner's behalf.

However, in every case, if you do not elect to receive such communications or if you elect to discontinue receiving them, then we will not send or will cease sending them to you. Also, we reserve the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement or regulatory investigation. Save for this, we do not sell, transfer or disclose personal information we have collected from you in connection with our web site activities, to third parties outside the McDonald's Family.

Please note that if we are, in turn, a promotional partner of an unrelated company, for example where we are not asking you to submit any personal information to us but are simply providing information on our site and there may be a link to the other company's web site where one must visit to take part in that company's promotion, offer or other activity, then the privacy policy of that other company will apply instead of ours.

Whilst we make every effort to only tie-in with reputable companies which have a similar high regard for your privacy, you should make sure you are aware of what their policies say, as we are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies, including those of other members of the McDonald's Family.

**Access**

You are in control of any personal information you provide to us on-line. If at any time, you would like to correct the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us or other members of the McDonald's Family, you can change your personal information by clicking on your name once you have logged in.

**Cookies**

ourlounge uses cookies to give you the best online experience.  If you would like to know more or change your settings, please read our Cookie Policy below which explains in more detail how cookies are used.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

From time to time, it may be necessary for us to change this privacy policy, so we suggest that you check here periodically. Rest assured, however, that any changes will not be retrospectively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions about our McDonald's Internet Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
McDonald's Restaurants Limited  
Customer Services  
11-59 High Road  
East Finchley  
London N2 8AW  
UK
